Associated Students of Duke University Records, 1965 - 1991 UA.31.02.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Executive, 1972-1990; 8
  - Executive Files, 1972-1990; 4
    - Vice-President at Large, 1978-1980 (Box 79)
    - VP at Large, 1981 (Box 79)
    - VAP at Large: David Cantrell, 1982 (Box 79)
    - VAP at Large: David Cantrell, Summer Correspondence, 1982 (Box 79)
    - VP at Large: David Cantrell, 1982 (Box 80)
    - VP at Large, Michael Scharf, "An Executive Brief", 1982-1983 (Box 80)
    - General, 1976-1981 (Box 80)
    - Memoranda, 1977-1978 (Box 80)
    - Memoranda, 1981 (Box 80)
  - Executive Council, 1972-1990; 5
    Executive Council subseries contains executive reports, minutes, and memorandum from meetings of the council. They also include a series of executive evaluations in which Duke administrators reviewed the performance of the executive and gave suggestions for improvement.
    - Administrative Secretary: Mary Kay Luke, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Applications, 1981 (Box 6)
    - Applications, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Budget Notes, 1981-1982 (Box 6)
    - ASDU Buisness Manager Files, 1985-1986 (Box 6)
    - By-Law Issues, 1987 (Box 6)
    - Committee Appointments, 1981 (Box 6)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 6)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1984 (Box 6)
    - Council of Presidents, 1982-1990 (Box 6)
    - Executive Evaluations, 1981 (Box 6)
    - Executive Evaluations, 1984 (Box 6)
    - Goals, 1987 (Box 6)
    - Judicial Review Board, 1987-1989 (Box 7)
    - Meetings and Agendas, 1981 (Box 7)
    - Memorandum, 1977 (Box 7)
    - Memorandum, 1978-1982 (Box 7)
    - Memorandum, 1980 (Box 7)
    - Minutes, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Minutes, 1985 (Box 7)
    - Minutes, 1987 (Box 7)
    - Minutes, 1990 (Box 7)
    - Philosophy, 1981 (Box 7)
    - Positions, 1989-1990 (Box 7)
    - Projects and Planning, 1980-1981 (Box 7)
    - Executive Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 7)
    - Executive Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
    - Executive Reports, 1981-1982 (Box 8)
    - Executive Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 8)
    - Speaker of the Legislature, 1988 (Box 8)
    - Student Affairs, 1982-1989 (Box 8)
    - Sutdent Organizations Chairman, 1981 (Box 8)
    - Vice President at Large, 1982 (Box 8)